newyorkdress.com 2019-04-05

# Privacy Policy

Effective date: September 1, 2011

New York Dress.com is committed to protecting your privacy. This privacy policy describes how New York Dress.com collects and uses the personal information you provide on our website: www.newyorkdress.com. It also describes the choices available to you regarding New York Dress.com's use of your personal information and the steps you can take to access this information and to request that we correct or update it. 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact New York Dress.com at info@newyorkdress.com.

**Collection and Use of Personal Information**

_Orders_  
If you purchase a product from us, we request certain personally identifiable information from you on our order form. You must provide contact information (such as name, email, and shipping address) and financial information (such as credit card number, expiration date). We use this information for billing purposes and to fill your orders. If we have trouble processing an order, we will use this information to contact you.

_Customer Service_  
When you place an order on our site, we will send you an email to confirm your purchase. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. We will communicate with you by email or telephone, in accordance with your wishes.

_Tell-A-Friend_  
If you choose to use our referral service to tell a friend about our site, we will ask you for your friend’s email address. A one-time email inviting him or her to visit the site will be sent via “Smile.io”.(see “Links to Other Sites” below for more information).

_Reviews/Testimonials_  
If you post a review on this Web site, you should be aware that any personally identifiable information you submit there can be read, collected, or used by other users of these forums. We post testimonials and comments received from our customers. We are not responsible for the personally identifiable information you choose to submit in these forums.

**Information Sharing and Disclosure**

We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell, rent, trade, or otherwise share your personal information with third parties except as described in this privacy statement.

_Agents/Service Providers_  
We use an outside shipping company to fulfill orders and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. We also utilize a fraud verification service to verify the validity of your credit card. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes.

_Legal Disclaimer_  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site.

**Log Files**

As is true of most Web sites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but your ability to use some areas of our site may be limited.

We use a third-party tracking service that uses cookies and tracking technologies to track non-personally identifiable information about visitors to our site in the aggregate to track usage and volume statistics. Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies and tracking technologies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by New York Dress.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any third parties.

**Clear Gifs (Web Beacons/Web Bugs)**

Our third party advertising partner employs] a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers’ personally identifiable information.

**Advertising**

We partner with a third party ad network to either display advertising on our Web site or to manage our advertising on other sites. Our ad network partner uses cookies and Web beacons to collect non-personally identifiable information about your activities on this and other Web sites to provide you targeted advertising based upon your interests.

**Links to Other Sites**

This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by New York Dress.com. Please be aware that we, New York Dress.com, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. When you use “AddThis" to bookmark and share our products and site, you will be taken to a third party site. Please note that these third party sites' privacy policies govern the collection and use of the information collected on those sites. This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

**Security**

The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at info@newyorkdress.com.

**Data Retention**

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services contact us at info@newyorkdress.com. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements.

**Business Transitions**

In the event New York Dress.com goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. 

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**

If your personally identifiable information changes, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by emailing our Customer Support at info@newyorkdress.com or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below.

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page.

**Contact Us**

| If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please contact us at:   
**NYD Trends   Inc.,**  
307 W 36 Street, 7 FL   
New York, New York 10018  
United States  
+1 (212) 594-3600 |   
---|---
